tecnick.com 2016-05-16

# Privacy Statement

This website uses only session cookies and does not use profiling cookies for the purposes of sending targeted advertisements. However, this site uses "third parties" cookies installed by different services than the site you are visiting. To disable the third-party profiling cookies, please visit the following links: [AddThis Targeting Opt-Out](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out "AddThis Targeting cookie Opt-Out") e [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin "Google cookie opt-out"). **By using this website, you agree to our use of cookies.**

The following statement outlines the privacy policy of Tecnick.com (www.tecnick.com). This policy is open to comment and is meant to provide an evolutionary framework from which we at Tecnick.com can address any concerns of the web-surfer community. Please forward any comments you may have regarding this policy to us at [info@tecnick.com](mailto:info@tecnick.com). 

## Third-Party Cookies

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google's use of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Consumer Data Collected by Tecnick.com

### Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data.

When you visit Tecnick.com site, we do not collect personally identifiable information regarding such individuals such as name, address, social security number or e-mail address. We do, however, collect what is known as statistic data. Statistic data includes information such as a web surfer's IP address, web pages which have been viewed by a web surfer, date and time, domain type, browser type, screen size and colors.  
The Non-Personally Identifiable Data that Tecnick.com collects is used for internal efforts to make a better and more useful site. The Non-Personally Identifiable Data may be shared with certain third party partners of Tecnick.com on a blind basis (e.g., broad demographic information relating to site statistics), but will never be provided to third parties in connection with personally-identifiable data or with any information which would allow a third party to directly link such information to a particular web surfer. If a web surfer has elected to provide Tecnick.com with personally-identifiable data and to allow Tecnick.com to utilize such data for various purposes, that data may be associated with the non-personally identifiable data for internal efforts. But, as set forth below, such linked data will never be shared with any third party (except for administrative purposes) or made available to the public. 

### Personally-Identifiable Consumer Data

Tecnick.com does not use any personally-identifiable data about a web surfer without first receiving the web surfer's consent. Examples of personally-identifiable data that may be requested include name, address, e-mail address, and social security number. Tecnick.com is committed to making sure that clear notice and choice is provided to all web surfers before any personally-identifiable data is used for any purposes beyond administrative purposes, for which such data is necessary. Tecnick.com will never request or collect data from a web surfer on subject areas including sexual orientation, political or religious affiliations, or medical data.  
All personally identifiable data provided by individual web surfers will be kept in strict confidence by Tecnick.com and will be treated with the same level of respect and care that Tecnick.com treats its other proprietary information and trade secrets. Tecnick.com will never sell, rent, exchange or barter any personally identifiable information to or with any third party for pecuniary gain or marketing purposes. Tecnick.com may, from time to time, provide such information to certain third-party administrative vendors for efficiency purposes in providing administrative services such as billing, delivery and pay-outs. Any third-party vendor so used, will be required to enter into a confidentiality and non-disclosure agreement with Tecnick.com upon terms and conditions consistent with the policies set forth herein.

### Security Precautions

Tecnick.com makes every effort to maintain the security of its site and the data we collect. Any data that is stored on Tecnick.com computers is treated as proprietary and confidential and is not available to the public. Tecnick.com has a strict internal security policy with respect to the confidentiality of data, limiting access only to those collaborators who have a need to know such information for the purpose of effectively delivering Tecnick.com services.

## Consumer Choice Concerning Data Collection

### Non-Personally Identifiable Consumer Data - Use of Cookies - Opt-Out.

While cookies are not essential to browse Tecnick.com site, they are necessary to login, buy items and access restricted areas.   
A web surfer may choose to opt-out of receiving the benefits associated with our use of cookies at any time by following a simple procedure to manually delete his or her cookies. Web surfers should refer to their respective browser's user manual for instructions on taking such action.

### Personally Identifiable Consumer Data - Opt-Out

Users can change or delete their personally-identifiable data simply using the user area or sending an email to [info@tecnick.com](mailto:info@tecnick.com).

### Children's Privacy

Tecnick.com is very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and makes every effort to protect the privacy of children surfing the web. Tecnick.com web site are not developed for or directed at children. If you believe your child has provided Tecnick.com with personally-identifiable data, or registered at one of Tecnick.com's web sites, and you would like to have them removed, please contact [info@tecnick.com](mailto:info@tecnick.com).

## Contacting Us

For more information or if you have questions or concerns regarding Tecnick.com's Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to [info@tecnick.com](mailto:info@tecnick.com).
